flylady.net 2006-12-19

# FlyLady.net: Privacy Policy

|  | 

## FlyLady and Company, Inc. Privacy Statement

>   1. **Statement of Intent:** At FlyLady and Company, Inc., nothing is more important than earning and keeping users confidence, trust, and respect. This philosophy applies to the website, e-mail list, chat boards, and discussion boards, and any other interaction users may have with FlyLady.net and FlyLady and Company, Inc. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to our Privacy Policy to ensure that the personal information is not misused in any way.
> 
>   2. **Personal Information:** Personal information such as name, time zone, and e-mail address is collected when users voluntarily register for membership services at FlyLady.net. This information will not be sold, rented, given, or disclosed to anyone outside of FlyLady and Company, Inc. unless such information is subpoenaed, or if FlyLady and Company, Inc. believes that membership has been used to commit unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health or safety of another user, person, or of the general public.
> 
>   3. **Aggregate Data and ISP Addresses:** FlyLady.net records ISP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to provide aggregate data to create reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors, and partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
> 
>   4. **Children Under 18:** No children under the age of 18 should submit or post to FlyLady.net without their parent’s approval
> 
>   5. **Yahoo! Groups:** Since we currently uses Yahoo! Groups' email system, please refer to [Yahoo Groups Privacy Statement](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for their Privacy policy. 
> 
>   6. **E-mail Lists are Opt-In:** Subscriptions to our e-mail list are opt-in and subscribers can opt-out at any time. Every e-mail sent to subscribers contains instructions on how to unsubscribe.
> 
>   7. **Cookies:** We may collect information about users that is not personally identifiable. This information might include the type of web browser or operating system you are using or the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our site. This type of information is similar to demographic information in section 3 and will be used in the same manner.
> 
> Additionally, FlyLady.net uses cookies to keep our site secure. If you are a member of FlyLady.net, you will be given a cookie as a "visitors pass." This lets you freely navigate our web site without having to present your credentials all the time. Depending on how you have configured your account, this cookie may stay for over a year, or last until you close your browser. You may have software on your computer that erases cookies, blocks them, or informs you before a cookie is stored. If that software interferes with the cookie operation, you may find yourself presenting your member credentials more than once. Refer to the documentation for your software for more information about how to control cookies.
> 
> FlyLady.net does not control any cookies you may receive from our advertisers and sponsors and these are not subject to FlyLady and Company, Inc.’s Privacy Policy.
> 
>   8. **Security of Information:** FlyLady.net cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. All transmissions are done at your own risk. Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, shall FlyLady.net or FlyLady and Company, Inc. be liable for any special, incidental or consequential damages that result from the use of the information or materials on FlyLady.net or the FlyLady’s email mentoring list.
> 
>   9. **Linked Sites:** This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by FlyLady.net and FlyLady and Company, Inc. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of linked web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of linked sites.
> 
>   10. **Please Talk To Us:** FlyLady and Company, Inc. welcomes your questions, comments, and concerns related to our Privacy Policy or any other aspect of our business. Please contact us at publicrelations@flylady.net to address any issues. Also you may send your comments and questions to:
> 
> FlyLady and Company, Inc.  
>  P.O. Box 1111  
>  Brevard, NC 28712
>   11.  **Changes to this Policy:** FlyLady and Company, Inc. reserves the right to update this policy at any time and without notice. Please check back frequently for updates to this policy.
> 
> 

> 
> USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR UNDERSTANDING AND AGREEMENT TO COMPLY WITH THE ENTIRE PRIVACY POLICY.
> 
> Copyright 2001, 2002, 2003 FlyLady and Company, Inc.
> 
> [Back](javascript:history.back\(\))

* * *  
  
---|---
